[BGM
Hmm
How I feel now
I'm hungry. I can't help it.
Ranrah, I'm a heavy senior.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry... I'm hungry...
We planted rice, harvested vegetables, went to meet farmers, went to a farmer's market.
We went to a research institute, met with sports kids, and did all sorts of other things!
I want to do a song that will surprise everyone.
Hmmm
How about a project like this?
How about a project where we go around the country and share all kinds of delicious food?
It's called "Zenkoku Uimono Uniform Tour" (All Japan Good Food Uniform Tour)
Sharing the goodies with others.
That's good! That's good!
Let's go with that.
Let's go, let's go!
Sorry I'm late.
How's it going? How's it going?
We just decided.
Oh, wow!
What is it?
What's the plan?
The plan for season 4 is
The National Good Food Safe Tour!
Sake Edition!
Sake?
Yes, with chopsticks and a bowl.
I was thinking that we could go around the country with chopsticks and a bowl.
Then we could eat good food anyway.
Wouldn't that be great?
I want to go to Kobe.
I want to go to Kobe and eat Kobe beef!
I'm so happy!
What about you, Moemi?What about you, Moomi-sensei?
I think I'd like to go to Hokkaido for milk.
But I also want to go to Okinawa.
I want to go to Okinawa!
Hey, you two...
Think seriously.
Yes, I am.
But there are so many things I want to do.
I don't know why.
Think about it.
While you're at it.
Where are we?
What year is it?
We're in Tokyo, Japan, and it's the year 2023.
Japan, 2023.
We made it!
Are you okay?
My stomach...
Tummy? Do you have a stomach ache?
Do you want me to call the researcher?
My stomach...
Here we are.
Oh, there you are.
What do you mean?
No, I mean, how did you show up?
Did you show up to get your cut?
No, wait, I didn't know where I was or when today was.
Maybe you're from the future.
LOL.
No, no, no.
You're too much Anga's wife.
You've been so busy lately.
You should get some rest.
Laughing.
Really?Really?
Are we there yet?
I'm hungry.
I'm learning Korean.
I like the taste of hot water roasting.
It tastes happy. Oh, man.
Hey, you know, it's great to be born in Japan.
The best.
Gohan. Rice, rice, rice, rice.
Oh, you're up?
You want to eat with us?
I'll eat.
This is out of the ordinary.
You look like you're going to eat it.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for helping me on this journey.
Well, I'll be moving on.
Well, I'm glad you're feeling better, really.
But, you know, you came in here on your own.
You just ate your dinner.
I don't know, it's just...
I'm sorry for intruding.
Can you at least tell me your name, where you're from, why you're here?
If you can't tell me what's going on, I'll call the police.
Please don't call the police!
You're gonna make me do it!
Can you at least tell me your name, or, you know, how you got here?
Mm-hmm.
My name is Matoba.
Matoba?
Actually, I'm...
I'm from the future.
I was in a time warp, and the coordinates got screwed up, and here I am.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
So you're from the future?Are you saying that you are from the future?
It's true.
People from the past, please believe me.
Past people?
If it's true that you're from the future...
Why did you come here?
Do you really believe me, Mui?
Let's just listen to him for once.
I believe you. Can you tell me what happened?
I came from Japan in the distant future.
The Japan of our time...
Japan is...
is full of hunger!
Hungry?
In the future Japan, or even in the world, there will be a shortage of food, and you will not be able to eat as much as you want, whenever you want!
There will be no milk or sponge cake in the future!
I don't care what you say.
There is so much to eat now.
It's hard to believe in such a convenient world.
It's true!
But in the future, the demand for food is increasing due to population growth.
But due to environmental problems, it is no longer possible to produce a lot of food.
And there are many other reasons.
But anyway, food is getting scarce and everyone is hungry!
Even this sponge cake will not exist in the future!
So you came here to change the future?
What? Alone?
Yes, I am. I'm an idol in the future.
Idol? What's it like to be an idol in the future?
Of course, they and their fans are hungry and lethargic all the time.
What is that? Are they going to be excited?
You know, idols and everything else is based on the body, right?
Well, if there's nothing to eat, there's nothing to do.
Have you ever heard of food security?
Food security...
No, I think I heard something about it on the news?No, I think I heard something about it on the news or something?
I knew I came to the right place at the right time...
Hmm? What's wrong?
Anyway! I came here to change the future.
There are people I want to help.
But I can't change the future by myself.
That's why I'm looking for someone to help me.
Because this sponge cake doesn't exist in the future...
Yum...
I'm both an idol and a researcher of idols.
I'm also a researcher of idols, and I'm also a researcher of idols.
I was searching for legends of past idols.
I found out that there is an idol group called "Niji no Konxador" who call themselves "Zen-Noh's Food Farming Group".
They are on YouTube to promote the appeal of Japanese food and agriculture.
I thought they might be able to help us.
I thought they might already be working on it.
So, I just jumped out of the plane.
Oh, I see.
Well, I'm kind of sorry about that.
Actually, we're the
We're the Rainbow Conquistadors.
You're Moe Tsurumi, from Kuisingo who loves to eat!
That's a little too much data for one word.
And you are Ao Yamato, the MC who chews a lot!
Marumaru!
I won't deny it, but...
Next to her is
Oh, Marina Kumamoto, the queen of muscle training!
Well, you're not wrong.
Thank you very much.
At any rate, my first mission is completed!
Of course, you all will help me, right?
Well, that's a bit sudden.
We have our own thing to do.
Like a nationwide wee wee wakizo trip.
We can always do that.We can always do that.
We just have to start facing it now, at this time.
Anyway, I can get you all to cooperate with me.
Please pass this on to the other members.
Now, in the meantime, I'd like to do some research on the past people.
Oh, I have to investigate grilled meat because cows are precious in the future.
Oh, and rice is also precious, so rice bowls too.
I'm busy, busy, busy!
Well, I'll be looking forward to working with you.
You don't have any cows?
And rice?
Anyway...
Let's eat sponge cake with soft cooperative milk.
Let's eat.
Yes, let's.
Good evening.
Hey, come in.
Please, sit here.
Thank you very much.
I'm hungry
Mr. Kazuneki, your usual curry, please.
Yes, please.
Here you go, sir. Our specialty curry and rice.
Thank you.
What's the matter, Marley? Trouble?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Bon appétit.
Thank you for watching.
Hey, Mr. Osechi.
I know this is a weird question all of a sudden, but...
Do you know the term "food security"?
Isn't that what food security is?
It's the idea of boosting domestic agriculture so that Japan won't have to worry about food in the future.
But isn't it also about having a balanced stockpile of food?
The point is that we should make sure that the food we eat is produced in our own country.
For that, we need people to produce, and it is also important to protect the natural environment of rice paddies and fields.To achieve this, we need people to produce, and it is also important to protect the natural environment of rice paddies and fields.
I'm just saying that we should think about various ways to lead a healthy life.
So you're saying that it's enough if farmers and nature are protected?
That's important, but there's more.
For example, where do the ingredients for the curry you're eating come from?
Of course the rice is Japanese rice, right?
The vegetables and meat are from somewhere in Japan, and the spices in the roux are from overseas.
So we're not just talking about Japan?
That's right. This is why we need to look not only at domestic markets, but also at overseas markets.
For example, what would happen if a country that exports curry spices suddenly stops importing them?
The meat that goes into it, the feed for pigs and cows, is usually imported as well.
This means that there is a possibility that not only curry, but also various foods that we normally eat without thinking about it, could be subject to such a situation.
So, the bottom line is that we have to deal with various problems in order to have food no matter what happens.
Hello?
Is he gone after all?
Where did he go?
Thank you very much.
Kyota, you still can't find him?
That's right.
He suddenly disappeared in the middle of a concert.
He didn't want to work alone, so he opened a store like this.
Thanks to you, it's thriving.
But I think it's time for me to start working as a comedian again.
Thank you very much.
Two thousand yen.
You left that much.
Yes, just right. Thank you very much.
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Here, take this home.
Yes, sir.
You two, take care of your food.
Here, take it home.
Wait, wait, wait. What? What do you mean?
Where did that come from?
Oh, um...
She's a hag from the future.She's a grandma, and she's from the future.
How did you get out?
I am Matoba, a future person.
I can do a lot of things that people from the past can't do.
Future man?
I've been to a lot of places and seen a lot of people in the past two days,
If there is such an abundance of food in the world, no one thinks it will ever go away.
I came here to change the future,
I realized that I alone cannot change the future.
I need to change the consciousness of many people.
I need the power of many people.
Hey!
Hey, Kyota!
Where have you been?
At a campground.
I was doing some research on this era, and I saw Kyota-san playing carefree at a campsite,
I bumped into him.
Hey!
This is the survey that Kyota helped me with
If the people of today work hard from now on
I'm sure that even in the future we will be able to eat our fill.
I want to tell that to as many people as possible.
You'll help me, won't you?
I know what you want to do, Matoba.
But...
But how do I tell people about it?
Don't worry about that!
We're having a work shampoo!
We are looking for participants!
We'll start with people who are interested in food security.
It's hard to solve it out of the blue.
But we'll think about it together.
If we all work together
We can change the future!
Matoma
I understand! Let's work together!Okay! Let's work together!
For our future!
Thank you! Let's change the future together!
Come on, even if you can't do it alone!
With our friends, we can do anything!
For our future!
Am I in your group?
I'm your partner!
And of course, Kyoda-san!
Okay! Tell me about the workshop!
Yes!
Well, what can I say when I'm hungry?
Osetsu-san, curry and rice for everyone, please!
Thanks again!
Yes!
New lesson!
Look up!
All of you!
Wow!
Powerful partners
It all started with a miraculous encounter
Todoke Sunsensers Season 4
For the future of Japanese food and agriculture
We all think about the significance of choosing domestic products
We look forward to seeing you at the workshop
We are looking forward to seeing you at the next workshop!
We look forward to seeing you next time!